{
    "id": "cdb9a75bd4d34475bbaa02251e5c5ce8",
    "title": "Past Tenses Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2c3310b485c74c8c8658ef2efe5b2e01",
            "title": "Past Tenses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She ………………………… college last year.",
                    "description": "Use the simple past to say when something happened in the past.",
                    "answers": [
                        "was leaving",
                        "left",
                        "had left"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our team ………………………… them yesterday.",
                    "description": "Use the simple past to say when something happened in the past.",
                    "answers": [
                        "had defeated",
                        "defeated",
                        "was defeating"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………. TV when dad arrived.",
                    "description": "The past continuous is used to talk about an action or situation that was going on at a particular point of time in the past.",
                    "answers": [
                        "watched",
                        "was watching",
                        "had watched"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "After she …………………………. her breakfast, she went to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ate",
                        "had eaten",
                        "was eating"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "By the time I reached the station, the train …………………………..",
                    "description": "The past perfect is used for the earlier of two past actions/ ",
                    "answers": [
                        "departed",
                        "had departed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………………… here yesterday.",
                    "description": "The simple past is used to say when something happened. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "came",
                        "had come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He …………………………… home late when the accident occurred.",
                    "description": "The past continuous is used for the longer background action that was going on when another action took place.",
                    "answers": [
                        "drove",
                        "was driving",
                        "had driven"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The guests had left before I ………………………… home.",
                    "description": "We use the simple past for the later of the two past actions.",
                    "answers": [
                        "reached",
                        "was reaching",
                        "had reached"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………….. sleep well last night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hadn't",
                        "didn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Every morning, he …………………………. for a walk.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was going",
                        "went",
                        "had gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………… when she heard the news.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was weeping",
                        "wept",
                        "had wept"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I thought of it just when you …………………………….. your mouth.",
                    "description": "The simple past is used to talk about two simultaneous short actions. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "was opening",
                        "had opened",
                        "opened"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}